<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hui-Jun Chen</title>
    <link>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hui-Jun Chen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 21:27:33 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://huijunchen9260.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:01:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About me Hi! My name is Hui-Jun Chen(陳惠鈞). I am a first-year Ph.D. student in the Department of Economics at The Ohio State University. My research mainly focuses on industrial organization. Before I arrived in the United States, I received my undergraduate and Master&amp;rsquo;s degrees in Economics at National Tsing Hua University, Taiwan (R.O.C.). My master thesis is about how multi-product</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 21:27:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/project/</guid>
      <description>The following computer programs are those I have written. Most (or all) of them are Linux-based programs, so they might not work on Windows, or even on MacOS. They are sorted in order on the frequency I use them and/or my priority to promote them.
 Dmenufm:  a simple file manager using dmenu and written in POSIX-compliant shell script. able to manage files with bulk selection mode corresponding vim plugin   Dmenubib  a simple bibliography manager using dmenu and written in POSIX-compliant shell script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 11:41:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Under construction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dmenufm Interesting Bugs</title>
      <link>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/blog/dmenufm_bugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 23:22:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/blog/dmenufm_bugs/</guid>
      <description>Dmenufm Interesting Bugs This is the interesting bugs that I encountered today.
This bug is the one I encounter when I try to implementing BulkListMass function after I finished implementing FM_EYE function.
The BulkListMass function is activated by selecting the variable $masselection in the ActionMenu. The functionality is good, but somehow FM_EYE seems to enter an endless loop, maximizes the usage of CPU, and eventually crash the whole system.
The reason for crashing is that I forgot to set the initial value for the $masselection variable, like masselection=&amp;quot;placeholder&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Hugo</title>
      <link>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/blog/hugonote/hugonote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 11:39:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/blog/hugonote/hugonote/</guid>
      <description>As a Ph.D. student, we all need to build or website to show our research and to introduce ourselves to the world. This post is my note on how to use Hugo, a static website generator, to build your own website and host it on GitHub.
GitHub part First of all, you need to sign up an account on GitHub. Details is on official website.
After signed up, you can press the icon on the top-right cornor and enter your profile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shell Scripting Tips</title>
      <link>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/blog/shelltips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 18:46:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/blog/shelltips/</guid>
      <description>fff Can add the following function to the /usr/bin/fff, put them in the case key() {:
Toggle executable flag.
${FFF_KEY_EXECUTABLE:=X}) [[ -f ${list[scroll]} &amp;amp;&amp;amp; -w ${list[scroll]} ]] &amp;amp;&amp;amp; { if [[ -x ${list[scroll]} ]]; then chmod -x &amp;#34;${list[scroll]}&amp;#34; status_line &amp;#34;Unset executable.&amp;#34; else chmod +x &amp;#34;${list[scroll]}&amp;#34; status_line &amp;#34;Set executable.&amp;#34; fi } ;; Open all Images
${FFF_IMAGE_OPEN:=I}) sxiv -ft * 2&amp;gt;/dev/null &amp;amp; status_line &amp;#34;Open all image in sxiv.&amp;#34; ;; Extract files.
${FFF_EXTRACTION:=O}) ext &amp;#34;${list[scroll]}&amp;#34; &amp;gt; /dev/null 2&amp;gt;&amp;amp;1 open &amp;#34;$PWD&amp;#34; status_line &amp;#34;Extraction complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Tips</title>
      <link>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/blog/archtips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 18:11:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huijunchen9260.github.io/blog/archtips/</guid>
      <description>Firefox cannot paste anything on facebook manager Reference: Solution Type about:config in New Tab, and search for dom.event.clipboardevents.enabled, and change the value to enable.
Get system info on command line uname -a
Clean orphan packages sudo pacman -Rns $(pacman -Qtdq)
Clean pacman cache Safe way:
Install pacchace first: sudo pacman -S pacman-contrib Then run paccache: - Delete all except three recent package: sudo paccache -r
Direct way: - Delete all: sudo pacman -Scc</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>